The apocalypse isn't for everybody.
Afterburn is a science fiction, action, comedy film directed by J.J. Perry.
Set against the backdrop of a postapocalyptic Earth whose Eastern Hemisphere was destroyed by a
massive solar flare, leaving what life remains mutated from radiation and fallout.
The story revolves around a group of treasure hunters who extract such objects as the Mona Lisa, the
Rosetta Stone and the Crown Jewels while facing rival hunters, mutants and pirates.
Jake, played by Dave Bautista.
Drea, played by Olga Kurylenko.
General Volkov, played by Kristofer Hivju.
Valentine, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Gorynych, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Fuentes, played by Eden Epstein.
Afterburn is a 2025 American post-apocalyptic action film directed by J.
Perry and written by Matt Johnson and Nimród Antal.
It stars Dave Bautista, Samuel L.
Jackson, Olga Kurylenko and Kristofer Hivju.
It is based on the Red 5 Comics graphic novel of the same name
by Scott Chitwood, Paul Ens, and Wayne Nichols.
The story is set a decade after the Earth's
technology was decimated by a solar flare.
Original development began in 2018, then halted, and restarted in 2024.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.